Steven, clearly, your focus are the tamale vendors.
That's clearly what you all are trying to get at.
Well, first of all, he uses the term — think about this.
He uses the term invasion force.
This fool, Governor Pritzker, uses the term invasion force to describe federal law enforcement.
He is adopting the language and the narrative of the paid insurrectionists and the Antifa
mobs.
The invasion force were the 20 million illegal aliens that Biden flooded into this country,
taking our jobs, taking our wages, filling up our hospitals, destroying God knows how
many schools, and, of course, leading to countless rapes, assaults, and murders.
That was the invasion force.
President Trump has elected on a mandate to turn that invasion back, to send those illegals
home.
Governor Pritzker is providing aid and comfort to the riotous mob that is physically assaulting,
obstructing, impeding, and attacking ICE officers.
And his latest act, declaring that there are no-go zones where federal law enforcement
is not permitted, is truly an act of insurrection against the federal government.
Do you anticipate the federal government will cite the Insurrection Act in order to ramp
up federal presence and federal presence kept safely in a city like Chicago?